Antibody is a action, horror, science fiction film
directed by Christian McIntire.
After a terrorist with an implanted nuclear detonator gets shot, a team of scientists must
defuse the bomb by miniaturizing themselves and going into his bloodstream.
His organism's antibodies start to mass against them.
Dr. Richard Gaynes, played by Lance Henriksen.
Dr. Rachel Saverini, played by Robin Givens.
Otto Emmerick, played by William Zabka.
Pacio, played by Gastón Pauls.
Trechak, played by Teodora Duhovnikova.
Amanda, played by Stella Ivanova.
Antibody is a 2002 science fiction thriller film directed and edited by Christian McIntire that
debuted as a Sci Fi Pictures TV-movie on the Sci Fi Channel on February 8, 2003.
The film explores themes of miniaturization, nuclear bomb, timebomb.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.